# DANIEL FASULA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

# CONTACT INFORMATION

208-447-0035 danielfasula@gmail

github.com/danielfasula

in linkedin.com/in/danielfasula/

# SUMMARY

Software Developer with 500+ hours of experience able to build web applications from the ground up - information gathering, planning, design, development, testing and delivery and maintenance. A fast learner with strong time management and multi-tasking skills. Strong work ethic in team or individual settings to drive product success and process efficiency.

## EXPERIENCE

#### **Code Works**

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT STUDENT FEB 2021 - APR 2021

- Developed over 30 web-based applications within 13 weeks with over 500+ hours of programming experience
- Experienced working in a team setting or as an individual to produce MVPs within proper time boxes
- Acquired the knowledge and tools to be able to apply SCRUM to a workload in order to produce quality work in appropriate amounts of time

#### **Certified Pharmacy Technician**

ST. LUKE'S OUTPATIENT PHARMACY | JUL 2020 - JAN 2021 CVS PHARMACY | OCT 2019 - JUL 2020 FRED MEYER | AUG 2018 - OCT 2019 ALBERTSONS | APR 2015 - AUG 2018

- Communicating with other health care providers, reviewing patient records, provide immunizations and filling medication orders while following HIPPA guidelines.
- In charge of overseeing multiple projects simultaneously
- Provide courteous customer service and assist the Pharmacist on duty in maintaining the clean and orderly appearance of the pharmacy area, prioritizing work, and processing prescription orders in compliance with Federal and State laws and company policies and procedures.

# SKILLS

- SASS
- FireBase
- C#
- Critical Thinking
- Confidence Creativity
  - Patience
- GitHubAuth0
- MongoDB
- Wireframing MVC
- Bootstrap Teamwork
- Restful API's

- Javascript
- Communication
  - HTML
  - Vue3
  - vue5
  - Node.js
  - Visual Studios
  - SCRUM /AGILE
  - Accountability

# APPLICATIONS

#### 710

- Application that allows users to have detailed logs of personal vehicles and vehicle maintenance. Gives the user the ability to store images of their vehicles and attach records or receipts for said maintenances.
- Worked in a team of 5 developers to create a web application with functional front-end and back-end
- Technologies used: Vue3, HTML, CSS, Animate.CSS, MongoDB, JavaScript, Firebase, Auth0, Bootstrap, Node.js
- Personally fulfilled the role of learning
  Firebase and being able to integrate it into the project, and helped create front-end and back-end functionality.

# EDUCATION

### **Code Works**

FEB 2021 - APR 2021

Certificate of Completion